♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... fam... ily... guy! ♪
I won a chain saw.
What? What are you talking about?
Some lady up the block is giving away
all of her husband's stuff
'cause he shot himself
- in the face.
- Oh, my god!
I've seen that lady.
He did the right thing.
That's also how we got this couch.
Basically everything in this house
is Christmas suicide furniture.
Donna, they had a bullhorn.
I don't know why,
but they had a bullhorn.
Cleveland, it's time for lunch.
What do I want? Sammich!
When do I want it? Now!
♪ I ain't eatin' no lipton soup. ♪
So, kids, bonnie just told me
about the neatest thing.
It's called a podcast.
I guess it's like a-a radio show
on your phone.
Have you heard of these? Podcasts.
Yeah, Mom, we know what podcasts are.
Huh.
I guess these types of things
take a while to reach the moms.
I'll have to let Bonnie know.
Wow, really?
Mom, Stewie needs his sausage cut
and his butter spread.
Here, let me get that for you, buddy.
There you go. Eat up, little guy.
Damn it, Peter.
You ruined Stewie's chair.
And Bonnie wants to know
what all the noise is.
- Amazing.
- Ooh.
- Wow, it's Willem Dafoe!
- That's right.
Since Willem Dafoe
has more bones in his face
than most people have
in their entire body,
he's perfect for carving,
'cause the angles are so sharp.
It's beautiful, Peter.
Yeah, I just love William Dafoe.
It's not "William," it's "Willem."
Yeah, that's what I said. "William."
He was in Spider-Man with Kristin Dunst.
- Kirsten Dunst.
- Right. Kirsten Dunce.
- It's not "Dunce," it's "Dunst."
- Yeah, Kristin Dunce.
In the movie,
she dated William Dafoe's son.
Spell it, Joe! Spell
what you are saying right now.
Well, I'll give it a shot.
K-Y-R-H...
Look, there's a reason I became
a cop and not a spellman.
- A what?
- A spellman.
- "Spellman" is not a thing, Joe!
- Sure it is.
Fireman, longshoreman, spellman.
Stop me when I'm wrong.
- He's getting too many right.
- Now I'm starting to think
there is such a thing as a spellman.
Hey, guys. Check it out.
- It's groot.
- Oh, yeah.
From that Marble movie.
What are you doing?!
- Turn that chain saw off!
- Not a chance, Lois.
You know how hard it was
to get that thing started?
It was even worse than trying to
cover anything with saran wrap.
Oh.
Perfect.
Can't wait to throw that out
in two weeks.
Peter! What's going on out here?!
Oh, hey, Lois.
I'm just hollowing out this tree
for the Keebler elves to live in.
- Awesome!
- I know, right?
Gonna get us a lifetime supply
of fresh-baked-but-still-stale
supermarket cookies.
All right,
time for a little elfin magic.
Ow! Oh! My arm! Oh, son of a bitch!
- Oh, my god!
- Mom, look.
Aw. Poor thing
must've been living in the tree.
- And its foot seems hurt.
- It's even worse than that.
It looks like the tree landed
on its parents and killed them.
Nobody touch
the smooshed squirrel bodies!
Ooh, I got to get my camera.
That girl is one giant red flag.
Stewie, this squirrel needs help.
I wonder if...
M-maybe I could take care of it.
I don't know if you should do it
on your own.
Could be a lot of work.
Would... Would you do it with me?
Well, I-I don't think it...
You know what? I think
that's a marvelous idea, Chris.
I daresay we would make
outstanding parents
- to this squirrel.
- Hey there, Griffin boys.
I saw this tree go down. Any loot in it?
Elven treasures?
Uh, no.
Hey, donna, the tree's just regular.
Go to work, Cleveland!
Well, somebody's getting big and strong.
Did you hear that one vet technician
say our little squirrel here
was in the 70th percentile
for height and weight?
No. Which vet tech said that?
The one with the neck tattoo.
- Which one with the neck tattoo?
- The one we saw
smoking in the parking lot
when we were leaving.
Again, you're gonna
have to be more specific.
The one wearing pajama bottoms as pants.
- Sorry, I don't...
- The girl one!
Oh, yeah, with the half-shaved
head. She was nice.
Well, I'll bet this cutie is hungry.
Wh-what are you doing?
Don't film me. Film the baby.
But you're both so cute.
This role, it-it suits you.
It's like you've been waiting
your whole life
to be this person.
Shush, you're going to make me cry.
Aw! He made a little toot.
That was me. It was
one of my cross-legged ones.
I should probably stop recording.
Well, if it's your elbow
that's bothering you,
we should start
by checking your reflexes.
- Okay, they seem all right.
- Oh, that's good.
But you got to help me.
My arm really hurts.
It all started after I got a chain saw.
Hmm, is that right?
Well, it sounds to me like
you may have chain saw elbow.
- "Chain saw elbow"?
- Yes, it's all explained
in this video.
Hi, I'm Tommy Lee Jones.
Congratulations on suffering
from the coolest arm ailment there is:
Chain saw elbow.
As a celebrity dick,
it's always been my passion
to own a ranch in a low-tax state
that I list as my primary residence.
And when I'm not pouting
at awards shows,
I'm out in the field cutting firewood
for a staged Instagram post.
Sometimes I overdo it,
end up with chain saw elbow.
Now here's fellow ranch owner
Dennis Quaid
to discuss the dangers of tractor ass.
So, you have tractor ass.
Okay, so how much
synthetic opioid do you need?
I'm trying to prescribe enough
to earn a fanny pack.
A-aren't there any other options?
Well, there's a trucker hat,
but those look stupid on me.
You know, sometimes joint pain
is connected to back issues.
Have you ever had
a chiropractic adjustment?
- What's that?
- It's a procedure
where a guy who couldn't
get into medical school
- tries to rip your head off.
- Does it work?
If you believe it works.
It's kind of like the polar express.
- Let's do it!
- Okay, I'll give it a shot.
But this type of thing
is usually done in strip malls
next to a little caesars.
Holy crap! What happened?
Well, I think we simply found
your true height.
Before years of poor posture
and wear and tear
- crushed your spirit and your spine.
- Wow.
Mr. Griffin, let's discuss risk factors.
Do you lead a lifestyle
that's sedentary?
Pet sedentary?
I'm saying you need
to strengthen your core
and exercise regularly.
- Is that the hat?
- Stupid, right?
I know the holidays
are still months away,
but I was just so excited
to take our family Christmas card photo.
Are you kidding? I love it.
You know what, Chris?
I feel like I'm ready to start trying...
To find another squirrel.
What?
Nothing. I just...
I just hit the lottery when I met you.
Here's your photo.
It's the only one where the squirrel
wasn't trying to bite your hand.
- Ooh!
- Oh, I love it!
- How much do we owe you?
- It's fine. Just keep it.
Sears just closed forever.
Whoa! Peter, what happened?
Did you tease that witch again?
No, I got a back adjustment.
Turns out I've been this tall all along.
- You don't say.
- Well, that's amazing.
Why are you still wearing
the same pants?
I don't know. I only get
pants at Christmas, so...
I'll get pants at Christmas.
- So, how is it being that tall?
- It's okay, I guess.
Although I've noticed I'm a lot
more clumsy in the bedroom.
I'm so sorry.
You two keep going.
I'm gonna clean this up.
Stewie! Stewie, come quick!
its first steps?
We've got to film this!
I know, I know!
Look at that!
Oh, I'm going to cry!
I've never felt this proud.
That's going on Instagram right now.
Totally! But we should
pair it with a song
about steps or walking.
Oh, my god, yes. "Walking on Sunshine."
Oh, that would sell it.
Sell what? That we're totally cliché?
- How about "Step by Step"?
- New Kids on the Block?
No. The Eddie Rabbitt version.
And have people think we're 100?
Let's do "Walking in Memphis."
I will concede that's a good song,
but we don't live in Memphis,
so I find it confusing.
What about "Walk Like an Egyptian"?
Well, we don't live in Egypt either.
Ah. Hoisted on my own petard.
"Nobody Walks in L.A."
Again, we do not live in L.A.
Ooh, let's do "I Love L.A."!
Do you know what?
This is going to surprise you, Chris,
but I agree with you.
Let's use "I Love L.A."
♪ I love L.A. ♪
- It's perfect!
- ♪ We love it! ♪
Yes, this will really tell people that
♪ I love L.A. ♪
♪ We love it! ♪
Thank you all for coming today.
It means a lot to Stewie and me
that you would be here.
I got this, Chris.
Everyone, after the service,
you are all invited to a small reception
to honor our beloved squirrel.
Nothing fancy.
Just acorns and puddle water.
It'll take place
either on top of the fence
or along a power line.
But, first, please join me
in a frozen-in-place moment of silence,
followed by a manic scattering
in all directions.
All right, the Quahog Fair.
Hey, Peter,
would you get off your phone?
Sorry, young girls
keep killing each other
'cause they think
I'm the Slender Man now.
Are-are you...
Are you telling them to kill each other?
It's just a goof.
You sure you're not too tall for this?
Nah, it's gonna be great.
Yay!
- Ow! Who kicked me?!
- Sorry!
- What the hell?!
- My bad.
- Ow! Who's doing that?
- It's that jerk up there!
It's Slender Man!
Kill yourselves!
- Peter!
- Come on. It's just a goof.
Don't you dare touch its bedroom!
The squirrel is gone, Stewie,
and there's nothing we can do
to change that.
Yes, thanks to you.
If it weren't for you,
our sweet baby would still be alive.
- Me?
- That's right.
If you hadn't kept the squirrel
up so late,
none of this would have happened.
That squirrel
should have been in bed, Chris.
It was 7:45!
What? I'm not the one
who just had to post the video
to Instagram that very second.
You couldn't even enjoy
the moment for one damn minute
before desperately groveling
for online approval
from aunts you never talk to
and past coworkers you don't even like!
Is that so?
Well, if you had a newer phone,
it wouldn't have taken so long
to upload the video.
Well, excuse me
for not having a fancier phone.
I'm only a paperboy!
Oh, I'm well aware
that you're only a paperboy.
Ah, perfect. I see you're using again.
Oh, I wonder why.
And don't think I didn't smell
the Charleston Chew
on your breath at the service.
Maybe if you'd been a little sharper
on the evening in question,
we wouldn't be in this...
I had four skittles that night!
That's not zero!
You knew there was a dog in the house.
He's practically your best friend!
Or maybe even more than that.
You shut your damn mouth!
Oh, this is awful.
Why does death seem so much
easier in the Rocky movies?
Goodbye, mick.
Oh, wai... you're just gonna
put him in a drawer?
- What are you, like, filing him?
- Yes, for tax reasons.
Jews don't die.
They just slowly depreciate
and then are eventually written off.
What's the matter, Peter?
I'm just sick of being tall.
I had a hard enough time getting
everything in the toilet before.
I want my old body back.
Well, there is a way.
What is it?
Lock the front door.
Peter, if you really want
to get shorter,
- I can berate you.
- What?
The female power to belittle is such
that the recipient can
physically shrink in stature.
That's why husbands and wives
are the same height in old age.
Lois, berate me.
Okay, Peter, but if I do this,
I really got to do it.
Do it.
For starters, you're a failure.
gah!
You didn't go to college.
Daddy pays our mortgage.
And you're a terrible husband
and father.
- Ouch!
- Your whole life
is a pattern of hateable noises.
- Ooh!
- The way you chew a banana
makes it sound
like it's filled with bones.
- Ouch!
- I loathe the little wheeze
at the crest of every breath you take.
- Yikes!
- I hate the one story you tell
at every cocktail party
about almost meeting John Kerry.
That's a good story.
You didn't even meet him!
Almost.
Your eyeglass lenses
have been smudged for 19 years.
Aw, crap.
Everyone hates it when you see fireworks
and you announce, "this is the finale!"
- Please stop.
- Pink Floyd is multiple guys!
He is?
You're so predictable.
I know every word that's gonna
come out of your mouth
before you even say it.
Balderdash. Heavens. Stop that.
I worked for purolator courier
before they went bankrupt.
Appearance.
Intelligence.
Penis size.
And another thing...!
Well, Lois, you are a master.
Well, let me first start by saying
y'all's doing
your relationship a huge favor
by coming to couples counseling.
Now, why don't y'all start
by each trying to suck up to me
so I can choose who I'm-a side with?
Well, I'm Stewart,
and I would love to offer you
a freshly baked brownie.
Mmm. Oh, my.
Someone's already in the lead.
I'm Chris. I'm somehow
both signing the checks
and always wrong.
See, this is why we came.
Right? It's this all day.
Oh, that's right.
I'm not allowed to mention
I'm paying for this.
It's both 100% true
and also the worst thing
anybody could possibly say.
He had his arms crossed
the whole ride here.
Excuse me if I don't buy into
this whole headshrinker business.
Stewie promised
he'd make healthy meals for us,
but all he ever makes is frozen pizza.
You said you loved pizza,
especially when I make
the ones with the crust
made of "hwheat."
He also does that.
Oh, really? Go ahead.
Show him those girls
you follow on Instagram.
It's all bosoms and derrieres on there.
This is all stuff I've talked
about with my life coach, Kyle.
Yeah, "life coach."
Kyle's into you and you know it.
What...?!
Okay. Chris, why don't you tell
your side of the story
while I share looks with Stewart
that say,
"whoa, this is
what you got to deal with?"
This is just so hard.
Stewie won't stop blaming me
about the death,
but it's not my fault.
I didn't kill our squirrel.
You know, I'm sad, too!
I know. I-I just...
I just don't know what to do
with all these feelings!
Which is why... I suppose I've
been taking them out on you.
I'm so sorry, Chris.
Me, too, Stewie.
We can't bring our baby back,
but we'll always have Tuesday
through Friday of last week.
Keep talking.
I's just gonna open up this big book
and use the time you're paying for
to figure out
when you're next available.
It was a true pleasure parenting
our squirrel with you, Chris.
Likewise, Stewie.
And although his life was brief,
I'll always have
very fond memories of him.
Wait, "him"?
It-it was a her.
No, it wasn't. The squirrel was a boy.
What? That's crazy.
- Chris, he was a boy.
- How do you know?
Well, you've got to check
with your finger.
But you really got to get it in there.
Huh. Well, then maybe it's better
that our baby you molested is dead.
Ooh, fudge!
"Don't be a grinch.
Please return plate to G. Quagmire."
Oh, great. So it's a gift and an errand.
Oh.
Oh, dear.
♪ I love L.A. ♪
♪ We love it! ♪
All right! New pants!